

Agus Wibawa Web Designer

+6281236261746 dekgusnfs@gmail.com aguswibawa.com Denpasar, Bali, Indonesia

EXPERIENCE

Web Designer

W&F Network Company

06/2021 - 07/2022

- Responsible for User Interface Company projects affiliate system site both live and template, 68 pages in total and 30 Layout template
- Prototyping Website using Figma and creating move motion on website using jQuery and css animation kit.
- Debugging website before live launch

Intern Web Designer

PT. Projasa

02/2021 - 04/2021

Internship web designer position for 3 months in newly open services for branding and marketing agency for 1 year

- Planning and Building Website project for client such for contractor and villa owner
- Helping UI Designer to mockup design for client project using Adobe XD
- Consulting Project progress to client

IT Admin

UD. Harsa Mandiri

12/2019 - 09/2020

- Creating Warehouse stock management system using Microsoft Access for daily and monthly reporting stock in, out and revenue.
- Maintenance Electronics tools in warehouse like CCTV, WiFi, and Other Admin Laptop.

Junior Web Designer

Deanna Day

02/2019 - 05/2019

- Building existing Mockup design into Homepage website using WordPress Elementor Plugin.
- · Designing Prototype Website for A/B Testing
- Designing Website component assets like images, icons also used for Brochure or Flyer

SUMMARY

Hi I'm Agus Wibawa my full name is Made Agus Wibawa Suyadnya. I'm Bali based Web Designer, UI/UX Designer with 3 years working experience in the same field I'm able to maintaining existing website and website that needed upgrade their layout interface design. I'm really enjoy designing and building a simple, innovative, and minimalist interface design, and always energetic, Quick Learner, well communicated person and easily adapt with your workflow.

SKILLS

Figma, Adobe XD, Adobe illustrator, Canva, Webflow

Advanced

Beginner

JavaScript, jQuery, JSX

Intermediate

ReactJS Framework
Tailwindcss and Sass

Intermediate

WordPress, Squarespace, Wix other CMS builder

Advanced

HTML5, CSS/SCSS

Advanced

LANGUAGES

Bahasa Indonesia

Native

English

Intermediate

EDUCATION

Information System

Institute Technology Stikom Balli Excellent at English Matriculation programs and TOEFL ITP Score 507